For a 40-year-old young engineer
He Slow Jogging
After pairing with diet
Glycated hemoglobin
From 12 to 6.2
High blood pressure dropped from 180 to 117
His three highs are really
slowly decreasing.
Three months
He lost 20 kilograms
Strength training
There are squats
Push-up
Every day
Exercise for about 10 minutes
Prevent falls
Hu Naiwen starts his lecture
I'm your old friend, Dr. Hu.
Hello, fans!
I have introduced super slow jogging
in the program before
Very popular
Today, I have specially invited
invited
the authority on super slow jogging for you
He helps a lot
Mature friends
An expert in regaining healthy physical fitness
Welcome, Instructor xú dòng yīng (transliteration)
Hi, Dr. Hu.
Hello everyone,
I want to share with you today
How to run Slow Jogging
No harm to knees, anti-three highs
Are you at risk for sarcopenia?
Tips for preventing falls
Let you
stay full of energy and maintain your functional abilities
in the second half of your life.
How powerful is slow jogging?
It strengthens the heart and lungs
Control the three highs
Instructor Xu
A fan asked me
He said he was old.
Blood pressure and blood sugar are unstable
After starting slow jogging
blood sugar is relatively stable
Among the students you lead
How many cases of the three highs are there?
In fact, there are many fans
Followed by slow jogging
His three highs
have a lowering effect.
Very good effect
I'll give you an example
A 40-year-old young engineer
He jogs Slow Jogging
After combining with diet
His glycosylated hemoglobin
From 12 to 6.2
His high blood pressure
From 180 to around 117
His blood lipids
From 230
Dropped to around 160-170
So his three highs
really decreasing slowly
Three months
He lost 20 kilograms
marvelous
The other one is 65 years old
He only spent two months
He just Slow Joggingevery day to catch up with TV series
Run for about two hours
Reach 20,000 steps
two months
It dropped from 200 to 86
Return to normal triglyceride values
Instructor Xu will share with you
about slow running later.
How to run effectively
How to run without hurting your knees
Be sure to watch till the end
Many doctors and nutritionists
They also encourage diabetics to start
with slow jogging
And you don't even need to go out
You just directly
After finishing your meal
you change your plan of taking a walk at home
to a Slow Jogging
It is very effective in stabilizing blood sugar
after meals
How long
after a meal can I run?
You just need
Rest for three to five minutes
You can run
Just three to five minutes
Yes. Why?
Because it's not very intense
Yes, it's not very intense.
Most importantly
When you sit on the sofa or lie down
You'll definitely wait for the next time.
You can't get up and run right away.
Then you will be lazy
Remember Instructor Xu's advice at this time.
You can
Start running from today
Actually slow jogging
Just a piece of cake for my course
My real main course is the core
People want to live a healthy life
Actually,
Core muscles must be strong
The center of gravity of our body
Our center of gravity muscles
No power
So your actions will be limited.
So walk slower
Poor mobility
Then started to have back pain
Shoulder and neck pain
Even my knees feel uncomfortable.
So we have to go through some
Resistance training Strength training
Let's make our muscles
Become strong and resilient
Your activity will improve
Back pain
difficulty climbing stairs
2 movements to detect sarcopenia.
Based on your experience
What are the signs?
Can detect yourself
Is it there?
The phenomenon of sarcopenia
If you feel that you
Getting out of bed
feels difficult
Also, I saw a low stool
Don't dare to sit down
Then climb the stairs with your hands
Sit in the car, unable to get out.
Have to use your hands to move your feet.
These are all signs of muscle loss.
It has slowly begun
to affect your life
Yes, this will definitely affect life
Next we can
Through two actions
To test your muscle strength
The first one is the isometric crunch for 60 seconds
Isometric crunches are a test of
your shoulder and neck strength.
The second one is straight knee leg raise
Straight knee leg raise is to test
your waist and abdominal muscle strength
Is it stable?
So what we did is a
Isometric Crunches
Please lie down after.
Bend your knees and open your feet about shoulder width apart
Don't spread your feet too far apart.
directly behind your hips
Then put your hands on your thighs
When curling up
Fingers, head, and shoulders
Slowly lift towards your knees
This action
Stay at the highest point for one minute
Good
Come on, let's get ready.
Alright, slowly start curling up.
10 seconds
At this time
You have to keep breathing normally.
20 seconds
If you can't hold on
You can put your knees
Lift your feet up.
30 seconds
Remember to keep your chin tucked
Don't lean back
40 seconds
So slowly
Return to rest
This is the isometric crunch.
This action
When doing it
If this muscle is not good
Your head and shoulders
It will keep falling down
If you fall down.
It means this muscle.
It can't last
That's actually relative to the human neck.
The compensation will be very serious
So it's not good here.
The shoulders and neck also get worse.
Before doing this action
I'll add an action first.
Just bend your knees and stretch your legs
Then we now
Let's demonstrate the movements
The first one we do
Lie down and test knee flexion
Can it be less than 90 degrees?
Let's put our hands on the floor.
Bend both knees, bring legs together, and lift them off the ground.
Keep your feet as close to your stomach as possible
Let your feet
The generated angle is less than 90 degrees
This is less than 90 degrees
This is about 90 degrees
If you say
Can shrink the belly
When it is less than 90 degrees
This means your hip joint
It's okay
Then we
When doing straight knee leg raises
Let's check again
Is your hip joint
Can be lifted to less than 90 degrees
Please put your hands together
Press on the floor
Keep your knees straight and together
Then our action
Do a simple test
We'll do it in three steps.
Come prepare
Inhale and slowly shrink up
Exhale, slowly lower down.
Inhale, come up.
That's a lot of viewers.
At the beginning
What will happen?
It's easy for him to bend his knees
Make it less than 90 degrees
But when you straighten your knees
He may be because
This muscle has no strength
He will appear like this
got stuck here.
That means
This muscle has no strength
Your back is fibrotic.
This is a
Caused by hip joint degeneration
So what if
If you don't hurry up
train this muscle
You will in the future
Always use your thighs to walk
Thigh walking and climbing stairs
Finally your knees
It starts to hurt
So you have to improve this
Please practice slowly
Bend your knees first, then straighten your knees
The effect is very good
The elderly are most afraid of falling
High CP value sports
Build muscle and prevent falls
Older friends
The most feared thing is not getting sick
It was a sudden fall
Especially in the bathroom and kitchen
That wet and slippery floor
Accidentally losing balance
Just fell down with a bang
Upside down
Hospitalization for a fracture is very troublesome.
Instructor Xu is like this
This sudden state of weakness
What should we do?
To protect yourself from getting hurt
The most important key
You still need to exercise your core muscles
core muscles
It's an airbag
When you are in crisis
It activates your core
Stable center of gravity
At this time you can
Reduce the risk of injury
Right
I will introduce you
Three high CP value muscle strength training
There are squats
Push-up
Push-up plank.
Just exercise for about 10 minutes a day
Engage your core muscles
After practicing
Prevent falls
Okay, now we
going to introduce you to squats.
Squat has a
Very important technique points.
It's your center of gravity
To fall on the heels
The center of gravity is on the heel
There will be
no previous knee problems
Then please follow me.
Feet shoulder-width apart or slightly wider
Less soft
It is recommended to be wider
Slightly wider than shoulders
The center of gravity is on the heel
Then start
Push your hip joint back.
Stretch your gluteus maximus to its longest
Center of gravity on the heels
Curl up your toes
Inhale and slowly squat down
Put your elbows on your knees and keep your head and chest out.
Exhale and slowly stand up
Inhale and squat
I would recommend
All audiences
Two to three days a week is enough
Just do it one or two days apart
Just one week
Do this two to three times
Do two to three sets at a time
That squat
One action can mobilize
Stimulates about 70% of the body's muscles
Its CP value is very high
Now for you
Introducing the second high CP value action
It's a push-up
He trains our upper body muscles
It is pushed by the palms
Motivate your shoulder joints
To train your pectoral muscles
Scapular muscles
When the elbow moves
Isometric contraction of
your biceps and triceps
wrist joint
Let your radius wrist front and back.
So, when you prone down like this.
Push your body up
Just build up your upper body muscles
Then I will introduce
Introductory version
Beginner Edition
Intermediate version
Then the standard version
We do four actions
That's because of time.
Every action we take
Just do it twice
Then you do this move
In case you can't
do the other three moves
You should do the most basic one first.
Do ten times
Do ten reps per set
Do about two sets at a time
Your effect
will practice slowly
That action
After practicing
Can effectively relieve
Your neck and shoulder pain
Even migraines
The cause of migraine
Usually this
Caused by the fibrosis of the trapezius muscle.
I train a lot of seniors.
had to take medicine
Migraine-induced headaches
Training for about three months
Half a year later,
his migraine was cured without medication.
So it’s important for me to introduce this
I hope that everyone
can study carefully and slowly.
The first one
We first do the kneeling elbow support
So how do we do that?
It is somewhat like a plank.
Please prone down first.
The most important thing is to prone down
Your shoulder joint needs to pronedown
You'd better use
Your chin touches the yoga mat
Then the shoulder joint
As close to the floor as possible
At this time we are kneeling and elbow support
So we kneel down
Dear audience,
can watch me demonstrate
Push up slowly
Push your body off the floor
Slowly bend your elbows down
Push up slowly
Do this 10 times
The effect is very good
When you do this
It's getting easier and easier
Then you do straight knee elbow push-ups
Your knees should be off the ground.
The shoulder joint needs to bend down.
Try to touch your chin to the yoga mat
Push up slowly
Hold up your whole body
Like a plank.
Slowly bend your elbows down
Push up slowly
Hold up your whole body
Slowly bend your elbows down
This is 10 round trips.
When you do this
Getting better and better
We then progress to using our palms to support
We call this kneeling and palm support
Then your palm
Where to put the push point
Don't be too forward
Pull back as far as possible
Pull to your
Keep your wrists and elbows as vertical as possible
Wrist and elbow perpendicular
So when pushing like this, use the base of your palm
Fingers slightly open
Push with the base of your palm
Same chin touching yoga mat
Push up slowly
Push your body off the floor
Kneeling on one knee
Slowly bend your elbows down
Push up slowly
Repeat this 10 times
Slowly bend your elbows down
Like this
After doing well
Let's move our knees away
It's the standard version
Push up slowly
Push your body off the floor
Slowly bend your elbows down
Push up slowly
I have been training seniors for more than ten years.
My observation
You'll improve if you just do it.
Don't deny who you are now.
When you get better and better
When your muscles are good
You can release
Your physical discomfort
good
The last action
What I’m going to introduce to you is the plank.
What about this action?
In fact, it is
Train your core
We just introduced the first two
One is squat
It's to train your lower limbs.
Push-ups to train your upper body
Plank, train your core.
These three actions
As long as you have time every day
Do three exercises times two sets
About six minutes
One minute for each movement
Six minutes, then a thirty-second break.
Just ten minutes
Keep your body in good shape
Now let's give
Let me introduce how to do the plank.
Alright, please slowly prone down in the same way.
Elbows about shoulder width apart
How to check shoulder width?
Cross your hands
When the hands are crossed
This is just about shoulder width.
Then open your hands slowly
You can put it in parallel
You can also put it in a triangle
Well, that depends on personal habits.
What is the most important thing?
Your shoulders and elbows should be vertical
Don't make the mistake at the beginning.
At this time, the shoulders lag behind the elbows
At this time
It will be very difficult for you to hold it up
It will be very strenuous for you to hold yourself up.
This one is too narrow
It's not okay if it's too slanted.
So when doing
Keep it vertical with your shoulders and elbows
This is very important
Okay, about shoulder width.
Arch your feet
Toes touching the ground
Then your neck
Try to look at the floor
Cervical vertebra looking at the floor
Don't look up
Don't bow your head either
Okay, ready.
Get ready for the timing
Come, start supporting your body
Contract your abdomen and straighten your core
At this time, there are six key points
First, keep your head straight.
Don't look down, don't look up
The second
10 seconds
Shoulders and elbows vertical
The third one is to tighten your abdomen
Fourth, squeeze your buttocks hard
Fifth, keep your knees straight.
Sixth, your ankle is at 90 degrees.
So, in the process of doing
Tighten your abdomen as much as possible
30 seconds
Then what
Breathe in and out slowly through your chest
40 seconds
Beginners can do it in 30 seconds
60 seconds is also possible
Do it according to your ability and take your time. You will be able to do it longer and longer.
50 seconds
60 seconds to
good
This is the plank.
Taiwan’s unhealthy life expectancy
7.78 years
Do this to avoid bedridden disability
According to statistics in 2023
The unhealthy life span
of Taiwanese people
7.78 years
What does it represent?
Represents the end of life
For almost eight years
Is bedridden
Disability
Living in a situation
where you need
care from others
Don't wait until you fall down to regret it.
If we
Take good care of your body and don't stay in bed
Don't let the children get involved, okay?
I often say
I would rather sweat more on the yoga mat
Less crying in bed
Want to prevent bed rest
I suggest you
Do these actions often
For example
Crunches
Second Bicycle Crunches
The third one is the hand-to-heel crunch
These three actions
You just need to put the positive core
You just need to train the front core
and the abdominal core on both sides
Introducing
Avoid bed rest
Main muscle groups trained
The first one
We are going to train
This is the piece
The source of the rectus abdominis muscle
Where does it grow?
Grows under the ribs
These are the upper four rectus abdominis muscles.
This muscle
If you become disabled.
You need someone to wake up
Hold your head and shoulders and hug you
It's the beginning of being cared for.
Please watch me demonstrate
Due to the filming.
Every movement we make.
Only do three to five reps
or three to five groups
This action is the same
Every action
Do ten reps or ten sets
Please watch me demonstrate.
Please all the audience
After sitting down slowly
Bend your knees
Open about shoulder width
Heels
directly behind buttocks
Place your hands on your thighs
When doing crunches
Fingers, head, and shoulders
Slowly do the same abdominal curling
Then lie down slowly
Then you lie down
It’s best if your elbows touch the ground.
Your head and shoulders
It's better not to land
What if really can't stand it?
It's fine even if you touch the ground.
The concept
Let's get ready
We'll do it three times.
Place your hands on your thighs.
Come ready
Getting Started
1 2 3
Come up and exhale
3 2 1
2 2 3
3 2 3
3 2 1
4 2 3
5 2 3
3 2 1
This is
Abdominal crunch training
Origin of the rectus abdominis
This muscle
mature age group
Exercise precautions
When they are exercising
What mistakes are easy to make?
How to avoid injury
In fact, I think the mature
Because there is too little muscle to train it
Then he'll be nervous.
When we are nervous,
we tend to hold our breath when we exert ourselves
What does holding your breath cause?
Dizziness
Will lack oxygen
It's easy to get hurt at this time
So remember
when we train strength training
Pay attention to your breathing
Through breathing rhythm
Let our muscles relax as much as possible
To achieve the effect of training
Key actions to lower blood pressure
Isometric contraction
What is isometric training?
According to the British Journal of Sports Medicine
His research showed
He said long-term practice
The so-called
So-called isometric contraction exercise
Can lower blood pressure
Make blood pressure more stable
Instructor Xu,
many people cannot understand what isometric contraction is.
Can you explain this
to our fans?
In fact, we
There are two modes of muscle training
A muscle that produces isotonic contraction
The second is isometric contraction
Isometric contraction
may allow our muscles
to maintain elasticity and flexibility
Isometric contraction
It improves your muscle tolerance
That old man
Isometric contraction is more important.
Because your muscles are not tolerant
Accidents are likely to happen
Suddenly
fell down because of the feeling of powerlessness
So the better your muscle tolerance is,
It is better for the elderly
I'll explain it this way.
Like the push-ups
we do with our bare hands
Get down and push up Get down and push up
The repeated distance is the same
Isotonic contraction
The plank
that we often hear about.
Muscle length remains unchanged when supported on the floor
Then count down
Holding in place with a countdown is called isometric contraction.
How should you run slow jogging the right way?
Can I run with a knee injury?
When we are doing slow jogging,
What kind of action
is the best
Now I will introduce four tips
to all the audience
With four key points.
That's what's most important to us
There are four tips
The first trick
Land on the sole of your foot first
Then lightly touch the floor with your heels
Dear audience,
You can see
My feet land first
The heel lightly touches the floor.
The heel should be barely noticeable, ideally.
This is the first tip
Land on the sole of your foot first
Then, the heel lightly touches the floor.
The second tip
Knees slightly bent
Dear audience,
Look at my knee joint.
It has never been straightened
Its joints
It is completely slightly curved
The third
Energy conservation and carbon reduction
When running
The sound of landing
It feels like practicing light kung fu.
The lighter the better
What about the fourth one?
To achieve energy conservation and carbon reduction
The best way
It’s small steps with a high step frequency.
180 steps per minute
You just follow this beat
Relaxing rhythm
Then, listen to your body with four key points.
These four tips
It's the body's feedback
Not sore.
No pain
Not hard
No panting
Soreness, pain, and shortness of breath don't look for you
You can run for a long time
Coach Xu has a book
heard it's just the first anniversary, right?
yes
This book was published on August 7 last year.
What about this book?
It's actually a tool book.
Chapter 2
There are standard and entry-level versions
There is a QR code
Scan Standard version action
There will be someone who will personally
shout out the commands and demonstrate the movements to you.
So this is the second chapter
My complete
Core muscle training course
Chapter 3 has a private menu.
This private menu
This is my experience of being a silver hair for 12 years
Share with everyone
Don't want back pain
Knee discomfort
Please do these six actions
Your back pain
won't bother you anymore.
The last one is called balance.
Tumbler training
Leg rest
For the elderly
This action is only necessary if it is done well
This action is guaranteed not to fall
as long as you do it well
So this book
is worth recommending
To all audiences
Question 1:
Many friends want to know
People with injured knees
Can they do slow jogging?
I still recommend
First undergo a doctor's evaluation
If you feel an injury in your leg.
If there is no problem
If there is no serious problem
You try it first
Stationary rhythm slow jogging.
That foot runs
If you don't feel uncomfortable
You can run
You'll feel uncomfortable running.
Of course don't do it first.
Stop for a moment
Question 2
Some people his feet
No strength to lift it up
How is this situation?
How to do Slow Jogging in this situation?
I would recommend
If he says he has doubts about lifting his foot
have difficulty
Maybe he has poor sense of balance.
I would suggest that he hold on to the wall first.
Then follow the metronome
Holding on to the wall
Standing rhythm slow jogging.
Just lift your feet off the ground a little
In fact, you move
Your mobility at this time
It will slowly get better
When you run better and better
You can leave the wall
Like I have a friend who had a stroke
He's probably in his sixties.
He held on to the wall
Just over a minute of running
out of breath and very tired
But I encouraged him not to give up.
Results after three months
He can run for an hour.
so good
Question 3
Ask about slow jogging
How long should you exercise every day?
There will be obvious effects
won't be so tired that I want to give up.
Actually slow jogging
It is a very effective aerobic exercise
One week we talk about
In terms of training frequency
Five to seven days a week
For example, if you want to lose weight
I'm a fan
He adds up to 90 to 120 minutes a day.
Combined with diet
For example, for 30 minutes each morning, noon and evening.
This will achieve
Just an hour and a half
right
You can take ten minutes, ten minutes, ten minutes
Accumulation is no problem
You just add up
Your daily running distance
Up to 90 to 120 minutes
Very helpful for weight loss and fat reduction
Combine with food
If you want to lower the three highs,
You run for about fifteen to thirty minutes.
After meals
So you run like this
Fifteen minutes times three
Is it forty-five minutes?
If you want to lower your blood lipids,
It's about 20 to 30 minutes.
That's twenty minutes times three.
Just sixty minutes
In fact, your blood fat
It slowly came down
good
very happy today
Instructor Xu shared so much with us
Exercise methods to make you healthier
I know
You don't want to be a burden to your children.
Health
is the best gift for your family
After watching this episode
Let's start
with son, daughter, father and mother tonight
All right
Which expert do you want to see me invite
to talk to me?
Please tell me in the comment section
Like this episode
Remember to click Super Thanks
Share the video with more people
Make everyone you love healthier